gyns.info 2012-12-27

# Privacy Policy - Domain-Street.com

**Privacy Policy**  
This Privacy Policy applies to collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by Domain-Street.com. If there are any exceptions, we will clearly disclose them prior to collecting any information, and will give you an opportunity to choose not to participate or provide the information. By using the Services and our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as we outline in this Privacy Policy. Domain-Street.com may decide to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post any changes here so that you are always informed of the information we collect, how we use it, and the circumstances under which we disclose it. Please be aware that, as part of the Services, Domain-Street.com provides links to Web sites operated by third parties, and also provides search results and similar services to third parties for display on their own Web sites or applications. Domain-Street.com is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices or the content of those third party Web sites or applications.

Domain-Street.com may collect any or all of the following four types of information:

·         (a) traffic or clickstream data,

·         (b) cookies,

·         (c) pixel tags or

·         (d) contact information and other personally identifying information.

(a) Traffic or Clickstream Data. Data about traffic and usage is not personally identifying or identifiable, and is not supplemented or combined with personally identifying or identifiable information. Domain-Street.com may share information it collects with certain selected third parties, but only in aggregated, anonymous form. For example, we may tell an advertiser that a certain number of people visited a certain area on our Web site, or searched Web sites for the term "basketball posters." Domain-Street.com collects some information regarding use of the Services by observing browser functions and the files (pages) users’ access. For example, Domain-Street.com's servers collect information about the site from which you entered to enable Domain-Street.com to calculate and pay its affiliates, information about the most frequently searched terms to help its advertisers provide the most relevant search results, information about usage to check for fraudulent behavior or other abnormalities and to ensure that our Services are technically superior. In addition to the foregoing applications, Domain-Street.com uses the information (in aggregate form) to better design the Services.

(b) Cookies. Like many sites, Domain-Street.com collects information about online behavior using cookies. These cookies contain identification information that enables us to see how our users are interacting with our site and how frequently they are returning, as well as to streamline their experiences using the Services. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information. Cookies let us know about repeat visitors and if we are delivering quality products and services. Domain-Street.com.com may also use cookies to identify which sites our repeat visitors are coming from, so that we can place more of our online advertising on these sites, and can, where necessary, pay our affiliates and other business partners. To Domain-Street.com, using information within cookies is an anonymous way to survey how we are doing and to look for ways to improve our Services. You may set your browser software to reject cookies, but you may not be able to use all of the features of the Services. Domain-Street.com may share information about usage of the Services with third parties, but only in aggregated, anonymous form. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

(c) Pixel Tags. Domain-Street.com shares web site usage information about visitors to our web site with a reputable third-party advertising company for the purpose of targeting our Internet banner advertisements on this site and other sites. For this purpose, Domain-Street.com and our third-party advertising company note some of the pages you visit on our Web site through the use of pixel tags (also called clear gifs). The information collected by Domain-Street.com and our third-party advertising company through the use of these pixel tags is not personally identifiable. For more information about our third-party advertiser, please click here. To opt out of the targeting program, please click here.

(d) Contact Information or Personally Identifying Information. Domain-Street.com can obtain access to your name, e-mail address and other contact information only (1) when you become a client with Domain-Street.com.com, provide comments, submit a problem, or request information from Domain-Street.com and provide your name or return contact information, or (2) in connection with special offers or contests. Contact information provided in connection with problems, comments or requests is used only to respond to those problems, comments or requests. This information is not stored or used in connection with traffic or clickstream data and is provided to a third party only as necessary to respond to the comment, problem or request. Finally, you may choose to provide contact information, other personally identifying information, and demographic information in order to participate in optional surveys or contests, which are run for promotional purposes. Domain-Street.com uses such information to send you information about its products and to notify you if you win the contest. Finally, from time to time, but only with your permission, Domain-Street.com may provide certain of its users' registration information to selected third parties who wish to participate in special promotions offered in conjunction with Domain-Street.com. Users may opt-out of receiving such communications at any time by contacting Domain-Street.com.

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, Domain-Street.com has put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information it collects online. However, data security is a constantly evolving art and science. You should consider any communication that you transmit to Domain-Street.com (such as data, questions or answers, comments, or suggestions) as non-confidential, and agree that Domain-Street.com will not be liable or responsible if information that belongs to you is intercepted and used by an unintended recipient.﻿﻿
